

# **ANI BEROSHVILI**

WEB DEVELOPER

### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Experienced professional with over 10 years in corporate insurance sales, specializing in client relationship management and negotiation. In 2023, transitioned into development, focusing on web technologies and programming. Actively seeking opportunities to apply newly acquired skills in front-end and full-stack development, driven by a passion for continuous learning and innovation.

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

- +995 577300480
- Beroshviliani100@gmail.com
- Tbilisi, Georgia
- https://ani-beroshvili.vercel.app
- https://github.com/anano303? tab=repositories
- in www.linkedin.com/in/ani-beroshvili-7a8998214

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- React Native
- CSS/SASS
- Angular
- JS/TS
- Node.js,
- React
- Express.js
- React
- Nest.js
- Next.js
- MongoDB

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Georgian(Fluent)
- English (Intermediate)
- Russian (Basic)

# **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

# **Back-end Development, Node. js**

Re-educate / 2024-Till today

Front-end Development, Angular

IT Academy Step | 2023-2024

Front-end Development, React/React Native

Skillwill | 2023-2024

**Master of Business Administration** 

Gerogian Technical University | 2013-2015

**Business Administration, Bachelor** 

Gerogian Technical University | 2009-2013 For more information, please visit: https://aniberoshvili.vercel.app/about

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **It Academy Step**

Front-End Developer Mentor | Sep 2024 - Present

#### Freelancer

Front-End Developer | Mar 2023 - Present

#### **BestSoft**

Web Developer | Mar 2023 - Present

**Prime Insurance Georgia** and other companies... Corporate Sales Manager | June 2012- Present

#### MY PROJECTS

Please explore my projects at the following link: https://ani-beroshvili.vercel.app/portfolio